NGUYEN PHONG VU

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

- **4** 03-05/2003
- **** 0784249942
- m www.linkedin.com/in/phongvudz
- https://github.com/phongvulearn ing
- https://phongvuportfolio.vercel.app
- vuphongnguyen030503@gmail.
- 32 Thuỷ Lợi, Phường Phước Long A, Quân Thủ Đức, TP.HCM

ABOUT ME

Front-end Developer with 2+ years of experience in React.js, TypeScript, and Tailwind CSS. Contributed to building the UrSlots SaaS platform, handling front-end and back-end development, and modernizing technologies for improved performance. In the next 2-3 years, I aim to become a senior front-end developer, focusing on performance, UX, and PWA development while leading teams and driving innovation.

WORK EXPERIENCES

Front-end Developer

04/2022 - Present

Gridly Company

- Developed and implemented various core features for the app, including merging branches, spell checkfunctionality, recording history, batch QA checks, importing localization, and facilitating real-time discussions.
- Suggested modern frameworks and libraries for the application, replacing outdated ones
- Researched and tracked new web technologies to enhance applications.
- Collaborated with backend team, integrating features, troubleshooting issues, and enhancing application functionality

Fullstack Developer (Partime) 12/2023 - Present Urslots (Start-up)

- Helped build key features of the app, such as authentication, appointment booking, categories, services, working hours, and, most importantly, import/export for bookings, staff, and clients.
- Enhanced app's UI and UX to achieve an aesthetically pleasing and user-friendly design.
- Collaborated on the development of a startup app, contributing to both front-end and back-end tasks for the creation of a cohesive and functional product.

SKILLS

HTML5 & CSS3 &

JavaScript & Typescript

NextJs

ReactJs

Responsive Design

Zustand, Redux

Git, Bitbucket, Jira, Github

React Hook Form, Framer Motion, Tanstack (Virtual , Router, Query) , etc.

EDUCATION

Self taught 06/2022 - 04/2023 **Self taught**

- Acquired foundational knowledge in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, and Tailwind CSS through self-study
- Built a personal project and learned how to deploy it, as well as use Git for version control to manage different versions of the project.

PROJECTS

Gridly

04/2022 - Present

Description: SaaS platform streamlining content management and localization for global products and digital teams.

- Improved performance by updating old frameworks and libraries.
- Built core features like real-time collaboration, spell check, localization import, and batch QA checks.
- Worked with the backend team to solve issues and improve app functionality.
- Kept up with new technologies and applied them to the project to stay up to date.

Site: https://app.gridly.com

Technologies: React.js, TypeScript, Tailwind CSS, Tanstack (Virtual,

Query, Router, Table), Zustand, etc.

UrSlots (Start-up) - Partime 12/2023 - Present

Description: A SaaS solution for nail salon bookings, designed to manage schedules, customer data, and appointments efficiently.

- Led full-stack development for UrSlots, a SaaS platform for booking services, implementing key features like authentication, appointment scheduling, import/export, and staff hours management.
- Improved UI/UX for a more intuitive experience, boosting user satisfaction and engagement.
- Collaborated with a small team to design scalable solutions for complex booking workflows, ensuring performance across the platform.

Site: https://dev-merchant.urslots.com/

Technologies: React.js, TypeScript, Hono.js, Redis, Cronjob, Tailwind CSS, etc.

Taskify (Self-project)

04/2024 - 05/2024

Description: A task management app with drag-and-drop functionality, similar to Trello, focusing on seamless workflow organization.

- Collaborate with team members
- Manage projects and tasks
- drag-and-drop task management
- · Customize task lists
- Mobile-friendly design

Site: https://taskify-app-phong-vu.vercel.app/

Technologies: React.js, Next.js, Tailwind CSS, Typescript, AivenDB, Prisma, Stripe

Frontend Mastery

07/2023 - 11/2023

Frontend Mastery Course

Completed a course on
 Optimizing React and Core
 JavaScript, gaining expertise in performance optimization, efficient state management, and best practices for building high-quality, responsive applications.

Learn on Roadmap

04/2024 - 07/2024

roadmap.sh

 Completed the Front End development roadmap as outlined on roadmap.sh to ensure a comprehensive understanding of frontend technologies

LANGUAGES

English (can communicate and meeting)

HOBBIES

- Enjoy play football
- Going out of drinks
- Explore new technology